Guide to the Yale University Press Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1910-1979; Accession 1990-A-042
  - Maio, Thomas, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 477)
  - Marley, Miss J., 1925 (Box 8, Folder 478)
  - Masef ield, John, 1916-1917 (Box 8, Folder 479)
  - Mason, Julian, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 480)
  - Mason, Lawrance, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 481)
  - Mather, S. Livingston, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 482)
  - May, Mark, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 483)
  - A.C. McClurg Company, 1912-1918 (Box 8, Folder 484)
  - McCook, Anson T., 1926 (Box 8, Folder 485)
  - McCrillis, John O.C, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 486)
  - McGill University Press, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 487)
  - Mellon, Paul, 1930-1937 (Box 8, Folder 488)
  - McKee, Oliver, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 489)
  - Meeks, Everett V., 1920-1936 (Box 8, Folder 490)
  - Melcher, Frederick, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 491)
  - Merrill, Charles, Jr., 1926 (Box 8, Folder 492)
  - Merz, Charles, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 493)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York, 1917-1937 (Box 8, Folder 494)
  - Meynell, Alice, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 495)
  - University of Michigan, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 496)
  - Miller, Alexander, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 497)
  - Mischer, Wendell, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 498)
  - Moore, Marianne, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 499)
  - Morehead, J.M., 1930-1937 (Box 8, Folder 500)
  - Morris, Charles, Mrs., 1917 (Box 8, Folder 501)
  - Morris, Edward, P., 1936 (Box 8, Folder 502)
  - Morris, Robert C., 1933 (Box 8, Folder 503)
  - Moseley, N., Mrs., 1930 (Box 8, Folder 504)
  - Moski, Bruno A., 1930 (Box 8, Folder 505)
  - Murray, Gilbert, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 506)
  - Myers, George Hewitt, 1915-1938 (Box 8, Folder 507)
  - Nairn, Gilbert, 1915 (Box 8, Folder 508)
  - The Nation, 1913-1917 (Box 8, Folder 509)
  - National Association of Book Publishers, 1928-1931 (Box 8, Folder 510)
  - Neeser, Robert, 1912-1915 (Box 8, Folder 511 - 512)
  - New Haven Post Office, 1911 (Box 8, Folder 513)
  - (New York) New Haven and Hartford Railroad, 1925 (Box 8, Folder 514)
  - The New Yorker, undated (Box 8, Folder 515)
  - New Haven Progress Exhibit, 1926-1927 (Box 8, Folder 516)
  - The New Republic, 1914-1918 (Box 8, Folder 517)
  - Nies, James B., 1918 (Box 8, Folder 518)
  - Norlin, George, Dr., 1939-1940 (Box 8, Folder 519)
  - Norton, W.W., 1930 (Box 8, Folder 520)
  - Notestein, Wallace, 1933-1939 (Box 8, Folder 521)
  - University of Oklahoma Press, 1930-1938 (Box 8, Folder 522)
  - O'Neill's "Touch of the Poet" Publication Party, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 523)
  - Orr, Lewis
    - 1925 (Box 8, Folder 524)
    - 1926 (Box 8, Folder 525)
    - 1927 (Box 8, Folder 526)
    - 1925-1928 (Box 8, Folder 527)
    - 1928 (Box 8, Folder 528)
    - 1929-1966 (Box 8, Folder 529)
    - 1928 (Box 8, Folder 530)
    - 1927 (Box 8, Folder 531)
  - Osborne, Thomas Mott, undated (Box 8, Folder 532)
  - Oviatt, Edwin, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 533)
  - Owen, Charles H., 1916 (Box 8, Folder 534)
  - Oxford University Press, 1909-1961 (Box 8, Folder 535 - 538)
  - Parsons, Francis, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 539)
  - Peabody Museum, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 540)
  - Penniman, James H., Dr., 1928 (Box 8, Folder 541)
  - University of Pennsylvania Press, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 542)
  - Percy, William Alexander, 1929-1930 (Box 8, Folder 543)
  - Perry, Ralph Barton, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 544)
  - Personnel Manual, 1964-1969 (Box 8, Folder 545)
  - Philadelphia University Museum, undated (Box 8, Folder 546)
  - Phillips, Duncan, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 547)
  - Plimpton Press, 1909-1918 (Box 8, Folder 548)
  - Porter, Arthur Kingsley, 1908-1917 (Box 8, Folder 549)
  - Pound, Ezra, 1915 (Box 8, Folder 550)
  - Pratt, Francis D., 1937 (Box 8, Folder 551)
  - Princeton University Press, 1925-1939 (Box 8, Folder 552)
  - Raushenbush, Stephen, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 553)
  - Reed, Edward Bliss, 1912 (Box 9, Folder 554)
  - Restarick, Henry, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 555)
  - Ripley, Alfred L., 1938-1940 (Box 9, Folder 556)
  - Ruche, Paul, undated (Box 9, Folder 557)
  - Rogers, Lindsay, 1918 (Box 9, Folder 558)
  - Rollins, Carl Purlington, 1924-1960 (Box 9, Folder 559 - 562)
  - Root, Elihu, 1929-1933 (Box 9, Folder 563)
  - Robinson, Edward S., 1934 (Box 9, Folder 564)
  - Robertson, Edwin W., 1925 (Box 9, Folder 565)
  - Rowell, Chester, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 566)
  - Rukeyser, Muriel, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 567)
  - Rush, Charles E., 1932 (Box 9, Folder 568)
  - Robert Rutter Company, 1912-1917 (Box 9, Folder 569)
  - Ruticka, Rudolph, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 570)
  - Salter, Arthur, Sir, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 571)
  - Charles Scribner's Sons, 1912-1916 (Box 9, Folder 572)
  - Sedgwick, Alice, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 573)
  - Serwude, Juseph, 1917 (Box 9, Folder 574)
  - Seymour, Charles, 1929-1937 (Box 9, Folder 575)
  - Sheffield, Mrs. G. St. John, 1925-1937 (Box 9, Folder 576)
  - Yale Shakespeare, 1918-1958 (Box 9, Folder 577)
  - Sheffield, James R., 1920 (Box 9, Folder 578)
  - Sharp, Cecil, 1917-1918 (Box 9, Folder 579)
  - Sherrill, Charles H., 1932 (Box 9, Folder 580)
  - Sihler, E.G., 1914-1932 (Box 9, Folder 581)
  - Sill, Louise Morgan, 1918 (Box 9, Folder 582)
  - Sizer, Theodore, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 583)
  - Societe Anonyme, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 584)
  - Soule, Phelps, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 585)
  - Soule, Ruth, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 586)
  - Smyth, Rev. Newman, 1913 (Box 9, Folder 587)
  - Stanford University Press, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 588)
  - Starett, T. Everett, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 589)
  - Louis Stern Memorial Fund, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 590)
  - Stimson, Henry L., 1932 (Box 9, Folder 591)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps - I, 1910-1916 (Box 9, Folder 592)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps - II, 1917-1939 (Box 9, Folder 593)
  - Stoddard, Louis, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 594)
  - Stone and Andrew Co., 1914-1915 (Box 9, Folder 595)
  - Street, Julian, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 596)
  - Studio Book Shop, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 597)
  - Suffolk Engraving Co., 1914-1916 (Box 9, Folder 598)
  - Sumner, William Graham, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 599)
  - Swindler, Mary H., 1934 (Box 9, Folder 600)
  - Taft, Robert A., 1934-1940 (Box 9, Folder 601)
  - Taft, William H., 1925 (Box 9, Folder 602)
  - Tate, Allen, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 603)
  - Taylor, Andrew S., 1939 (Box 9, Folder 604)
  - Tercentory Commission of -the State of Connecticut, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 605)
  - Thomas, A.S., 1914 (Box 9, Folder 606)
  - Thompson, Dorothy, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 607)
  - Thompson, George, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 608)
  - J. Walter Thompson Co., 1910-1935 (Box 9, Folder 609)
  - Thorp, Margaret Ferrand, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 610)
  - Tilson, John Q., 1926 (Box 9, Folder 611)
  - Tinker, Chauncy B., 1936-1939 (Box 9, Folder 612)
  - Toland, Edward B., 1939 (Box 9, Folder 613)
  - Torrcy, Charles, 1916-1918 (Box 9, Folder 614)
  - Toscanni, Arturo, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 615)
  - Truman, Harry, 1956-1958 (Box 9, Folder 616)
  - Tuttle, Emerson, 1931-1937 (Box 9, Folder 617)
  - Union and New Haven Trust Co., 1928 (Box 9, Folder 618)
  - University Presses, 1924-1968 (Box 9, Folder 619)
  - University Press Association, 1916-1918 (Box 9, Folder 620 - 623)
  - Updike, D.B., 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 624)
  - Vanderbilt, Mrs. W.D., 1930 (Box 9, Folder 625)
  - Van Riper, Walker, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 626)
  - Vassar College Publications, 1914-1915 (Box 9, Folder 627)
  - Warner, Lloyd, 1939-1940 (Box 9, Folder 628)
  - Wasson, R. Gordon, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 629)
  - Watkins, T.H., 1939 (Box 9, Folder 630)
  - Watrous, Eliot, 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 631)
  - Webb, Elizabeth, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 632)
  - Weismiller, Edward, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 633)
  - Weitenkampf, Frank, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 634)
  - West, Rebecca, undated (Box 9, Folder 635)
  - Wetmore, Monroe, 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 636)
  - Whitehead, Philip B., 1914 (Box 9, Folder 637)
  - Whitney, John Hay, 1928-1937 (Box 9, Folder 638)
  - Williams., Mrs. Harriet Trumbull, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 639)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 640)
  - Wilder, Thornton, 1931-1939 (Box 9, Folder 641)
  - Williamstown Institute of Politics, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 642)
  - Wilson, Robert Forest, undated (Box 9, Folder 643)
  - Witlington, Robert, undated (Box 9, Folder 644)
  - Woolsey, John W., 1933 (Box 9, Folder 645)
  - World War I, 1917 (Box 9, Folder 646)
  - Yale Alumni Authors, undated (Box 9, Folder 647)
  - Yale Alumni Weekly, 1925-1939 (Box 9, Folder 648)
  - Yale University Athletic Association, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 649)
  - Yale Banner and Potpourri, 1926-1930 (Box 9, Folder 650)
  - Yale University Class Book, 1916-1917 (Box 9, Folder 651)
  - Yale Club of New York, 1926-1934 (Box 9, Folder 652)
  - Yale Daily News, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 653)
  - Yale University Dramatic Association, undated (Box 9, Folder 654)
  - Yale Educational Television, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 655)
  - Yale University Faculty Manuscripts, 1947-1959 (Box 9, Folder 656)
  - Yale University Fund Raising, 1957-1958 (Box 9, Folder 657)
  - Yale University Library, 1909-1918, 1926-1940 (Box 9, Folder 658 - 659)
  - Yale Literary Magazine, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 660)
  - Yale Review
    - 1926-1932 (Box 9, Folder 661)
    - 1932-1936 (Box 9, Folder 662)
    - 1937-1941 (Box 9, Folder 663)
    - 1939-1959 (Box 9, Folder 664)
    - 1951-1964 (Box 9, Folder 665)
    - 1949-1960 (Box 9, Folder 666)
  - Yale Seal, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 667)
  - Yerkes, Roberta W., 1929-1939 (Box 9, Folder 668)
  - YUP Archives, 1958-1968 (Box 10, Folder 669)
  - YUP Archives - potential material, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 670)
  - YUP Archives - Misc. correspondence, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 671)
  - YUP General History: YUP Library Bookplates, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 672)
  - 60th Anniversary YUP, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 673)
  - Exhibits - 75th Anniversary, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 674)
  - Homes of the Press
    - Photos, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 675)
    - Articles, 1908-1959 (Box 10, Folder 676)
    - II, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 677)
    - 149 York Street Purchase, 1957-1959 (Box 10, Folder 678)
    - 149 York Street Opening, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 679)
  - Press Personnel Policies, 1915-1958 (Box 10, Folder 680)
  - YUP Authors - General, 1930-1949 (Box 10, Folder 681)
  - YUP and Scholarly Publishing, 1932-1957 (Box 10, Folder 682)
  - Prizes - Administrative, 1953-1967 (Box 10, Folder 683)
  - Prizes and Exhibits, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 684)
  - Prizes: Manuscript, 1961-1967 (Box 10, Folder 686)
  - Prizes: Submission Unnecessary, 1961-1965 (Box 10, Folder 687)
  - National Book Awards, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 688)
  - Book Awards and Exhibits, 1924-1959 (Box 10, Folder 689)
  - Legal Affairs / Seal, 1916-1946 (Box 10, Folder 690)
  - YUP Inventories and Appraisals, 1928-1968 (Box 10, Folder 691)
  - YUP Board of Directors, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 692)
  - YUP Governing Board, 1951-1986 (Box 10, Folder 693)
  - YUP Annual Report, 1913-1938 (Box 10, Folder 694)
  - YUP Annual Report - II, 1940-1958 (Box 10, Folder 695)
  - Council's Committee on Publications
    - 1929-1951 (Box 10, Folder 696)
    - 1908 (Box 10, Folder 697)
    - 1909 (Box 10, Folder 698)
    - 1910 (Box 10, Folder 699)
    - 1911 (Box 10, Folder 700)
    - 1912 (Box 10, Folder 701)
    - 1913 (Box 10, Folder 702)
    - 1914 (Box 10, Folder 703)
    - 1915 (Box 10, Folder 704)
    - 1916 (Box 10, Folder 705)
    - 1917 (Box 10, Folder 706)
    - 1918 (Box 10, Folder 707 - 708)
    - 1924, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 709)
    - 1926 (Box 10, Folder 710)
    - 1927, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 711)
    - Reports to, 1928-1929 (Box 10, Folder 712)
    - Reports to, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 713)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 10, Folder 714)
    - 1932-1938 (Box 10, Folder 715)
  - Yale Press Governing Board, 1939-1945 (Box 11, Folder 716 - 717)
  - Council's Committee on Publications, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 718)
  - Yale Press Publications Committee, 1951-1954 (Box 11, Folder 719 - 720)
  - Minutes of Governing Board and its Executive Committee, 1953-1957 (Box 11, Folder 721)
  - YUP Publications Committee, 1955-1957 (Box 11, Folder 722)
  - Committee on Publications
    - 1964 (Box 11, Folder 723)
    - 1963 (Box 11, Folder 724)
    - Minutes, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 725)
    - 1959-1961 (Box 11, Folder 726)
    - 1962 (Box 11, Folder 727)
  - Editorial Department
    - 1929-1964 (Box 11, Folder 728)
  - Editorial: Rejected Manuscripts
    - 1909 (Box 11, Folder 732)
    - 1910 (Box 11, Folder 733)
    - 1911 (Box 11, Folder 734)
    - 1912 A - E (Box 11, Folder 735)
    - 1912 F - Z (Box 11, Folder 736)
    - 1913 A - K (Box 11, Folder 737)
    - 1913 L - Z (Box 11, Folder 738)
    - 1914 A - L (Box 11, Folder 739)
    - 1914 M - Z (Box 11, Folder 740)
    - 1915 (Box 11, Folder 741)
    - 1916 A - L (Box 11, Folder 742)
    - 1916 M - Z (Box 11, Folder 743)
    - 1917 A - C (Box 11, Folder 744)
    - 1917 D - K (Box 12, Folder 745)
    - 1917 L - P (Box 12, Folder 746)
    - 1917 Q - S (Box 12, Folder 747)
    - 1917 T - Z (Box 12, Folder 748)
    - 1918 A - L (Box 12, Folder 749)
    - 1918 M - Z (Box 12, Folder 750)
  - Editorial Early Reader (for Manuscripts), 1918 (Box 12, Folder 751)
  - Editorial Report Slip, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 752)
  - Editorial: Patterson Prize Essays, 1940-1956 (Box 12, Folder 753)
  - Editorial (Box 12, Folder 754)
  - Yup Style Manual, 1915-1959 (Box 12, Folder 755)
  - Marking Copy, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 757)
  - Manuscripts Submitted, 1955-1966 (Box 12, Folder 758 - 759)
  - Permissions, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 760)
  - Title Pages, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 761)
  - Yale Press Archives: Press Projects, 1933-1953 (Box 12, Folder 762)
  - Editorial: Copyright Office/Library of Congress, 1929-1932 (Box 12, Folder 763)
  - Editorial Hours, 1960-1966 (Box 12, Folder 764)
  - Benjamin Franklin
    - 1923-1954 (Box 12, Folder 765)
    - 1954-1960 (Box 12, Folder 766)
  - YSYP General Information, 1941-1960 (Box 12, Folder 767)
  - Yale Series of Younger Poets Management
    - 1924-1926 (Box 12, Folder 768)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 12, Folder 769)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 12, Folder 770)
    - 1932-1934 (Box 12, Folder 771)
    - 1934-1940 (Box 12, Folder 772)
    - 1940-1946 (Box 12, Folder 773)
    - 1946-1954 (Box 12, Folder 774)
    - 1968 (Box 12, Folder 775)
  - Early Book Reviews, 1911-1939 (Box 12, Folder 776)
  - Book Reviews - News Releases, 1933-1935 (Box 12, Folder 777)
  - Publication Department, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 778)
  - Printing and Book Publishing - General, 1924-1930 (Box 12, Folder 779)
  - Manufacturing and Printing Office
    - 1917-1933 (Box 12, Folder 780)
    - 1934-1961 (Box 12, Folder 781)
    - 1939: Printing Office Survey (Box 12, Folder 782)
  - Promotion
    - Misc. Advertising, 1911-18 (Box 12, Folder 784)
    - Misc. Advertising, 1961-1963 (Box 12, Folder 785)
    - Yale U. News Releases, 1932-1936 (Box 12, Folder 786)
    - Sales Promotion Letters, 1930-1934 (Box 12, Folder 787)
    - Early Advertising Copy, 1913-17 (Box 12, Folder 788)
  - Sales, 1917-1963 (Box 12, Folder 789 - 791)
  - Finances: General, 1923-1958 (Box 12, Folder 792)
  - Finances: Early Balance Sheets, 1909-1910 (Box 12, Folder 793)
  - Finances: Early Paid Bills, 1908-1918 (Box 12, Folder 794 - 795)
  - Internal Revenue, 1917-1938 (Box 12, Folder 796)
  - Social Security, 1936-1937 (Box 12, Folder 797)
  - Advertising, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 798)
  - Archives, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 799)
  - Vinland Map, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 800)
  - Published Books Announcements, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 801)
  - Book Awards, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 802)
  - Book Catalogues - Spring, Fall Paperbound, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 803)
  - Hellmut Lehman-haupt: Gutenberg and the master of Playing Cards, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 805)
  - Carroll L.V. Meeks: Italian Architecture 1750-1314, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 806)
  - John H. Ostrom and John S. McIntosh: Mash's Dinosaurs: the Collection from Como Bluffs, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 807)
  - James Tate: The Lost Pilot - YSYP Winner, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 808)
  - Vinland Map Articles, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 809)
  - Claude-Ann Lopez: Mon Cher Papa: Franklin and the Ladies of Paris, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 810)
  - Vinland Map cont., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 811)
  - American Institute of Graphic Arts Booklet-Award Winners, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 812)
  - Association of American University Presses-Book Awards, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 813)
  - University Presses Directory, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 814)
  - University Presses Miscellany, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 815)
  - Miscellaneous News Articles, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 816)
  - Miscellaneous Press Information, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 817)
  - Christmas Card, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 818)
  - Press Personnel, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 819)
  - Printing Office Samples, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 820 - 821)
  - Promotion Materials: Samples, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 822)
  - Advertising, Sales, Miscellaneous Promotion, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 823)
  - Mohawk Paper Company Catalogue with YUP Books, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 824)
  - Peabody Museum Centennial - Yale News Bureau Release, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 825)
  - Miscellaneous New Articles, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 826)
  - Book Awards, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 827 - 828)
  - Published Books Announcements, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 829)
  - Book Catalogues - Spring, Fall Paperbound, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 830)
  - Catlin: 0-kee-pa, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 831)
  - Goldstein: The Insanity Defense, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 832)
  - Vinland Map, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 833)
  - Holden, Reuben A.: Yale: A Pictorial History, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 834 - 835)
  - Yale Press Authors, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 836)
  - Miscellaneous Press Information, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 837)
  - Press Personnel, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 838)
  - AIGA Catalogue, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 839)
  - AIGA Fifty Books Show, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 840)
  - AAUP Book Show, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 841)
  - Publication Announcements, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 842)
  - Advertising and Promotion, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 843)
  - Advertising, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 844)
  - Printing Office Samples, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 845)
  - Book Covers, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 846)
  - Published Book Announcements, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 847)
  - Paperback Book Covers, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 848)
  - Book Catalogues - Spring, Summer, Fall, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 849)
  - Press Authors, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 850)
  - Hine Bartletts' West, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 851)
  - YUP Computer, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 852)
  - Promotion News Releases, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 853)
  - Advertising Tear Sheets, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 854)
  - Press Memoranda, Personnel Info., 1968 (Box 14, Folder 855)
  - Book Covers, YUP Printing Office, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 856)
  - Book Jackets, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 857)
  - Helen Chasin "Coming Close" YSYP, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 858)
  - Advertising, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 859)
  - Book Catalogues, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 860)
  - Printing Office Samples, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 861)
  - Personnel, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 862)
  - Advertising, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 863)
  - Book Jackets, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 864)
  - Promotion Events and Activities, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 865)
  - Press Releases, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 866)
  - Yale Series of Younger Poets, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 867)
  - Press Authors, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 868)
  - Book Covers, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 869)
  - Paperback Book Covers, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 870)
  - Published Book Announcements, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 871)
  - Carl Purlington Rollins: P.O.
    - Stationery Samples, Greeting, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 872)
    - Awards, Diplomas etc., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 873)
    - Pamphlets and Booklets, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 874)
    - Bookplates, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 875)
    - Inter-Office Memos, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 876)
    - Posters and Signs, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 877)
  - Promotion and Advertising, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 878)
  - YUP Authors, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 879)
  - Book Jackets, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 880)
  - Paperbound Book Covers, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 881)
  - Published Book Announcements, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 882)
  - Publication Announcements, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 883)
  - Josef Albers 80th Birthday Party - YUP Library, undated (Box 15, Folder 884)
  - Yale University Press Personnel Manual, undated (Box 15, Folder 885)
  - J.E.E. Fletcher Esq. YUP - File with U.S. Government, Private, 1912 (Box 15, Folder 886)
  - Agreement between YUP and Yale University, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 887)
  - Assignment to Yale Publishing, Association of the Yale Review, 1907 (Box 15, Folder 888)
  - Salary Payments to Mr. George Parmly Day beginning 7/1, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 889)
  - Film Service, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 890)
  - Mad Bomber phone call to Press - 1/19, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 891)
  - Mr. Hadly letter to Mrs. Whitelaw Reid - 1/27, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 893)
  - Copies of Letters Written to Employees - 2/15, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 894)
  - Trademark Registration Material, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 895)
  - Letters, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 896)
  - Yale Publishing Association, Inc. to YUP Inc. Bill of Sale, undated (Box 15, Folder 897)
  - Agreement between Yale University and G.P. Day et al. - 10/11, 1908 (Box 15, Folder 898)
  - Bill of Sale: Yale Review sold to YUP by Yale, Publishing Association, Inc. - 12/3, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 899)
  - Out for Territory List - 0. for T. memos, Contract Information Sheets, undated (Box 15, Folder 900)
  - Personnel Policy and Fringe Benefits, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 901)
  - City of Wichita, Administrative Personnel Policy and Procedure Manual, undated (Box 15, Folder 902)
  - Publishing Information, undated (Box 15, Folder 903)
  - Chronicles of America, undated (Box 15, Folder 904)
  - Chronical Lists of the Books in the YUP Library, undated (Box 15, Folder 905)
  - YUP Library - Current File., 1967 (Box 15, Folder 906)
  - Notes on Missing Books and the Ledger Dates, 1961-1962 (Box 15, Folder 907)
  - Master Lists of Missing Books, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 908)
  - Photocopies of Public and Maintenance Directions for the G.P. Day Library, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 909)
  - Friends of the YUP, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 910)
  - YUP Newsletter, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 911)
  - Dead Matter, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 912)
  - Dead Matter (misc.), 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 913)
  - YSYP Inquiries, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 914)
  - M-Z (YSYP), undated (Box 15, Folder 915)
  - Yale Series of Younger Poets, 1963
    - A (Box 16, Folder 916)
    - B (Box 16, Folder 917)
    - G (Box 16, Folder 918)
    - H (Box 16, Folder 919)
    - I, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 920)
    - J, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 921)
    - K (Box 16, Folder 922)
    - L (Box 16, Folder 923)
    - MC, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 924)
    - M, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 925)
    - N, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 926)
    - 0 (Box 16, Folder 927)
    - P, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 928)
    - Q (empty)
    - R, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 929)
    - S (Box 16, Folder 930)
    - T (Box 16, Folder 931)
    - U (Box 16, Folder 932)
    - v (Box 16, Folder 933)
    - W (Box 16, Folder 934)
    - XYZ, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 935)
    - Inquiries, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 936 - 937)
    - Management
      - 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 938)
      - 1965 (Box 16, Folder 939)
      - 1964 (Box 16, Folder 940)
      - 1965 (Box 16, Folder 941)
      - 1961-1963 (Box 16, Folder 942)
    - Michael Harnett - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 943)
    - Management, 1950-1966 (Box 16, Folder 944)
    - Inquiries and Entries, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 945)
  - Miscellaneous Invitations, Pamphlets, Addresses
  - Historical Background of YUP
  - Miscellaneous Magazines, Newspaper Clippings, Pamphlets, undated (Box 17)
  - Chronicles of America: Pageant of America; Correspondence
    - Allan Nevins, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 946)
    - National Committee for Study of Social Values in Motion Pictures, 1929-1930 (Box 18, Folder 947)
    - The North American Review, 1926-29 (Box 18, Folder 948)
    - Robert E. Norton, undated (Box 18, Folder 949)
    - Henry A. Ogden, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 950)
    - Lansing P. Reed, 1929 (Box 18, Folder 951)